Capital District Regional Planning Commission; Records apap380
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Saratoga County, 1960-2008; 2; 9.68 cubic ft.
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Financial Report, 1963 July (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Generic Draft Environmental Impact Statement for Clifton Park Plan for Development, 1989 June (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement for Clifton Park Master Plan, 1989 August (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Environmental Quality Review, New Elementary School No. 8, 1987 September (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Final Report-Crescent Road Corridor Study, 1988 June (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Focus on Clifton Park [Newspaper Supplement], 1980 November (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Hydro Geologic Investigation of the Colonie Channel Aquifers, 1981 August (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Hydrogeology of the Clifton Park Area [Maps], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Land Use Analysis, 1963 November (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Master Plan of Development Part 1: Goals, Policies and Land Use Plan, 1989 November (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Master Plan of Development Background Papers No. 1-4, 1987 May (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Master Plan of Development Background Papers No. 5-8, 1987 July (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Master Plan Statement of Findings, 1989 October (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Neighborhood Analysis, 1964 February (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, New York, Master Plan, Vol. 2, 1965 March (Oversized 2)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Population Study, 1963 June (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Synopsis of Master Plan Study and Report of the Planning Consultant [Map], 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Transportation Study, 1964 January (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Western Clifton Park Land Conservation Plan and Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement (1 of 2), 2004 October (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Western Clifton Park Land Conservation Plan and Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement (2 of 2), 2004 October (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park and Halfmoon, A Community Study, 1974 February (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Corinth, Community Goals and Objectives Proposed Land Use Plan, 1977 September (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - [Town and Village of] Corinth, Community Information Survey: Analysis and Tabulation, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - [Town and Village of] Corinth, Growth Factors Report: Population, Housing, Economics Transportation, Public Facilities and Services, 1976 November (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - [Town and Village of] Corinth, Town Visual Analysis, Village Visual, Environmental and Historical Inventory and Analysis, 1976 November (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Day, Natural Resources and Community Information Report, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Edinburg, National Resources and Community Information Report, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - [Town and Village of] Galway, Comprehensive Development Plan, 1970 May (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Galway, Local Law No. 1 of 1968, Contains All Revisions Through March 8, 1988, 1988 December (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - [City of] Glens Falls, Zoning Use Schedule, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Comprehensive Plan, 1990 April (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] Greenfield, Background Studies/Land Use Plan, 1974 December (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Greenfield, Land Use Plan -Summary Report, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Greenfield, Official Zoning Map, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Greenfield, Subdivision Regulations, 1996 February (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Greenfield, Update of the Comprehensive Land Use Plan and Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 1990 December (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] Greenfield, Zoning Law, 1997 October (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] Hadley, Natural Resource Report, Preliminary Draft, 1976 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Hadley, Preliminary Land Use Inventory and Plan, Report No.1, 1975 January (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - [Town of] Hadley, Proposed Land Use Code Report No. 2, 1975 February (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - [Town of] Halfmoon, Application for the Old Champlain Canal Trail, 2004 November (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - [Town of] Halfmoon, Comprehensive Development Plan, 1971 July (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Halfmoon, Comprehensive Plan, 1971 July (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Halfmoon, Engineer's Report Proposed Water Improvement, 1980 May (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Halfmoon, Local Laws Relating to Zoning, 1990 November (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Halfmoon, Local Laws Relating to Zoning, 1997 February (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Halfmoon, Master Plan, 1972 April (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Halfmoon, Subdivision Regulations, 1990 November (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Malta, Final Comprehensive Master Plan and Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 2000 December (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Malta, Luther Forest Environmental Impact Statement, 1978 October (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Malta, Luther Forest Environmental Impact Statement (1 of 2), 1981 January (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Malta, Luther Forest Environmental Impact Statement (2 of 2), 1981 January (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Malta, Master Plan, 1987 December (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] Malta, Master Plan, 1988 March (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Malta, Plan for Malta, 1966 January (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Malta, Statement of Findings, Malta Town-Wide GEIS, 2006 June (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - [Town of] Malta, Subdivision of Land, Chapter 143, 1998 October (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Malta, Zoning, Chapter 167, 1999 February (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Mechanicville, Application for Workable Program Certification or Re-Certification, 1971 October (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mechanicville, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Mechanicville Public Library, 1988 August (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - [City of] Mechanicville, Housing Code, 1962 August (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Milton, Draft Comprehensive Plan 2001, 2001 January (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Milton, Zoning, Chapter 180, 2008 April (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Moreau, Comprehensive Plan, 1966 December (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Moreau, Moreau Industrial Park Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement (1 of 2), 1991 January (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Moreau, Moreau Industrial Park Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement (2 of 2), 1991 January (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Moreau, Moreau Industrial Park, Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 1991 August (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Moreau, Moreau Industrial Park, Infrastructure Development, 1991 January (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Moreau, Subdivision Regulations, 1990 March (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Moreau, The Zoning Law, 1998 May (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Moreau Lake State Park, General Camping Information, 1970 May (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Northumberland, Zoning Ordinance, 1995 April (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Round Lake, Location of Substandard Units, Round Lake Historic District, 1980 June (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Round Lake, Round Lake Association 1868-1968, 1968 August (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Saratoga County, 1980 Census Information Saratoga County by Tract, 1985 October (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Saratoga County, Adaptive Reuse Proposal Washington Bath, 1984 February (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga County, Administration Manual for the Local Planning Process, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Saratoga County, Agricultural Inventory, 1975 June (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Saratoga County, Airport Master Plan, Saratoga County Airport, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Saratoga County, Assorted Newspaper Clippings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Saratoga County, Atlas of Towns and the Outside District of Saratoga Springs, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Saratoga County, Comprehensive Intermunicipal Public Water Supply Study (1 of 2), 1968 July (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Saratoga County, Comprehensive Intermunicipal Public Water Supply Study (2 of 2), 1968 July (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Saratoga County, Comprehensive Sewerage Study Volume 2, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Saratoga County, Comprehensive Sewer Study Bend of the River Area, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Saratoga County, Comprehensive Sewerage Study of Saratoga County NY, Volume 1, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Saratoga County, Comprehensive Sewerage Study of Saratoga County NY, Volume 2, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Saratoga County, Construction and Service Agreement Between County of Saratoga and (Company), Draft, 1987 March (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga County, County of Saratoga Department of Highways Combined Project Information Report 2 and Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1972 May (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Saratoga County, Design Report Phase 2 Interstate Route 502 Rest Area and Comfort Station Construction (1 of 2), 1973 September (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Saratoga County, Design Report Phase 2 Interstate Route 502 Rest Area and Comfort Station Construction (2 of 2), 1973 September (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Saratoga County, Directory of Human Services, 1974 June (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Saratoga County, Draft 1975-76 "701' Housing Element, 1976 May (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Saratoga County, Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement Solid Waste Management Plan, 1989 December (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Saratoga County, Draft Water Supply Plan Abstract, 1971 February (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Saratoga County, Economic Profile, 1977 September-1977 December (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Saratoga County, Educational Facilities, 1975 December (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Saratoga County, Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement Solid Waste Management Plan (1 of 2), 1990 April (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Saratoga County, Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement Solid Waste Management Plan (2 of 2), 1990 April (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Saratoga County, Final Report: A Water Quality and Watershed Study of Loughberry Lake, 1988 June (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga County, Focus on Saratoga County Mobile Home Parks, 1971 March (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Saratoga County, Focus on the Poor in Saratoga County, Survey of Needs and Services, 1973 November (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Saratoga County, Gear '89 Saratoga, Ride Maps, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Saratoga County, General Geologic History of Saratoga County and Evaluation of Related Resources, 1975 April (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Saratoga County, Glens Falls Area Report on Intermunicipal Public Water Supply, 1967 March (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Saratoga County, Government Structure: Present and Future, 1979 August (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Saratoga County, Ground-Water Studies in Saratoga County, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Saratoga County, Guide to Technical and Financial Assistance for Economic and Business Development Leaders, 2002 April (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Saratoga County, Hadley-Lake Luzerne Joint Sewerage Project Wastewater Facility Plan (1 of 2), 1978 August (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Saratoga County, Hadley-Lake Luzerne Joint Sewerage Project Wastewater Facility Plan (2 of 2), 1978 August (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Saratoga County, Housing, [Saratoga County Planning Board Report], 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga County, Human Services Needs Assessment, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Saratoga County, Industrial Resources Survey of Saratoga County, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Saratoga County, Inventory of Community Facilities in Saratoga County, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Saratoga County, Land Use and Development Plan, A Draft, 1977 June (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Saratoga County, Land Use and Development Plan, 1978 January (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Saratoga County, Land Use and Development Plan, 1978 January (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Saratoga County, Municipal Directory of Planning and Zoning, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Saratoga County, Overall Economic Development Program, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Saratoga, Overall Program Design, 1974 September (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Saratoga County, The People of Saratoga County, New York, Trends in Human Resources and their Characteristics 1900-1960, 1968 August (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Saratoga County, Policy Framework for Land Use and Development Plan, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Saratoga County, Preparing a Blueprint for the Future, Saratoga County Twenty First Century Commission, 1987 October (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga County, Present and Future Vocational Education Needs, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Saratoga County,… Preservation of Viable Farm Land in the Clifton Park-Halfmoon Region of Southern Saratoga County, 1980 September (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Saratoga County, Public Scoping Session for the Saratoga Spa State Park Master Plan, 1983 April (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Saratoga County, The Recreation Potential for Saratoga County, 1970 August (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Saratoga County, Report of the Shenendehowa Senior Housing Development Committee, 1980 September (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Saratoga County, Report of the Southern Saratoga Citizens' Transportation Committee, 1980 September (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Saratoga County, Report on Comprehensive Sewerage Study Including Mohawk River Drainage Basis, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Saratoga County, Report on the Formation of Saratoga County Sewer District No.1, 1968 December (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Saratoga County, Report on the Formation of Saratoga County Sewer District No.1, 1969 June (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Saratoga County, A Report on Recreational Needs of Southern Saratoga to the "Springboard for Success" Workshop, 1980 October (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga: A Marketing and Programming Study of the Saratoga Mineral Baths and State Park, 1982 September (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga '85 Planning Board, 1985 October (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga Convention and Tourism Bureau Brochures, Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County Bikeways Study, Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County Correctional Facility, Preliminary Report, 1979 October (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County Correctional Facility Study, 1980 February (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County Industrial Profile, Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County, N.Y. Sewer District No. 1, Appendix to Final Report (1 of 2), 1975 October (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County, N.Y. Sewer District No. 1, Appendix to Final Report (2 of 2), 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County, N.Y. Sewer District No. 1, Final Report, 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County Overall Economic Development Committee Progress Report, 1979 June (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County Park-and-Ride Lot Plan, 1993 May (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County Solid Waste Management Facility Project, SEQRA Draft, 1986 July (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga Solid Waste Management Facility Project Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 1986 November (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga County Transit Needs Assessment, 1985 January (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga Lake Aquatic Weed Harvesting Program, A Summary, 1984 December (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga Lake Phase 1 Diagnostic Feasibility Study and Management Plan, 1983 September (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga Lake Phase 1 Diagnostic Feasibility Study and Management Plan, Executive Summary, 1983 September (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Saratoga County, Saratoga Performing Arts Center, [Promotional Brochure], Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Saratoga County, Sewer District No. 1 Wastewater Facilities Report, 1970 May (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Saratoga County, Sewer Study, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga County, Soil Descriptions, 1991 March (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Saratoga County, Soils Map, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Saratoga County, Soil Survey Maps of Saratoga County, Sheets No. 1-26, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Saratoga County, Soil Survey of Saratoga County (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Saratoga County, Soil Survey of Saratoga County (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Saratoga County, Soil Survey of Saratoga County, New York, Interim Report, 1995 May (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Saratoga County, Soil Survey of Saratoga County, New York [Missing Map], 1917 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga County, Southern Saratoga County Chamber of Commerce Business Directory, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Saratoga County, Subdivision Regulations, 1963 June (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Saratoga County, Summary Comprehensive Sewerage Study, Volume 1, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Saratoga County, Supplement to Wastewater Facilities Report of May 1970 for Saratoga County Sewer District No. 1 (1 of 3), 1976 August (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Saratoga County, Supplement to Wastewater Facilities Report of May 1970 for Saratoga County Sewer District No. 1 (2 of 3), 1976 August (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Saratoga County, Supplement to Wastewater Facilities Report of May 1970 for Saratoga County Sewer District No. 1 (3 of 3), 1976 August (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Saratoga County, Vischer Ferry Nature and Historic Preserve Master Plan, 1996 August (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, 1987 Master Plan [Draft] (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, 1987 Master Plan, 1987 June (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Application for the Saratoga Spring Downtown Greenwat-Spring Run Trail Project, 1997 April (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Application for Workable Program Certification, 1970 April (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Application for Workable Program Certification or Re-Certification, 1974 February (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, A City in Transition: A Master Plan for the City of Saratoga Springs (1 of 2), 1960 July (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, A City in Transition: A Master Plan for the City of Saratoga Springs (2 of 2), 1960 July (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, City School District Middle School, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1988 July (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - [City of] Saratoga County, Community Development Block Grant 1998 Entitlement Action Plan, 1998 May (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Community Development Block Grant 2001 Entitlement Action Plan, 2001 May (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Community Development Block Grant 2002 Entitlement Action Plan, 2002 May (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Community Development Block Grants Entitlement Program 2005 Consolidated Plan, 2005 June (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Community Profile [Info Sheet Prepared by Niagara Mohawk Area Development Department], Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Comprehensive Development Plan, 1970 May (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Executive Summary of the 1996 Entitlement Action Plan, 1996 July (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, "Growing a City in the Country": 1999 Comprehensive Plan, 1999 May (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Historic Congress Park, Master Plan Report, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, [Informational Brochure], 1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Saratoga, Local Law for the Regulation of Mobile Homes and Mobile Home Parks and Travel Trailers and Trailer Camps, 1974 June (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, A Marketing and Programming Study of the Saratoga Mineral Bath and State Park, 1982 July (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, National Museum of Racing and Hall of Fame [Brochure], 1991 April (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Plan of Action, 1974 March (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Proposed Charter of the City of Saratoga Springs, 1984 November (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, Spring Valley North Urban Renewal Plan, 1971 March (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - [City of] Saratoga Springs, West Side Neighborhood Needs Assessment, 1981 October (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - [Villages of] Schuylerville and Victory, A Comprehensive Plan (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - [Villages of] Schuylerville and Victory, A Comprehensive Plan (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - [Village of] South Glens Fall, Comprehensive Plan, 1966 December (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - [Village of] South Glens Fall, Environmental Assessment Part one, Project Information, 1982 March (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - [Village of] South Glens Falls, Environmental Assessment Part 1: Waste Water Facilities, 1982 March (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Stillwater, Background Studies, 1972 December (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Stillwater, Comprehensive Plan, 1973 December (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - [Town of] Stillwater, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Stillwater Elementary School, 1987 June (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Stillwater, Proposed Land Use, 1972 December (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] Stillwater, Proposed Zoning Ordinance, 1973 July (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Victory Mills, Re: SNC Hydro Inc.'s Application for Amendment of License for the Victory Mills Hydroelectric Project, 1985 December (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] Waterford, Environmental Impact Statement for Riverbend (1 of 2), 1981 January (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Waterford, Environmental Impact Statement for Riverbend (2 of 2), 1981 January (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - [Village of] Waterford, Flood Insurance Study, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Waterford, Official Minutes, Public Hearing, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Riverbend, 1981 April 2 (Oversized 2)
  - [Town of] Waterford, Plan for Waterford, 1965 April (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Waterford, Proposed Amendments to the Town of Waterford Zoning Ordinance, 1990 September (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - [Town and Village of] Waterford, Recreation Master Plan Study of the Erie Barge Canal, Concept Map, 1975 November (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - [Town and Village of] Waterford, Report on Wastewater Treatment Facilities, 1972 December (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Waterford, Riverbend- Conceptual Design, 1979 August (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Waterford, Supplement to Draft Environmental Impact Statement-Riverbend, 1981 April (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Application for Land and Water Conservation Funds, 1986 September (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Development Report Update, 1999 February (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Development Report Update, 2001 January (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Development Report Update, 2002 January (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Development Report Update 2007, 2008 January (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Subdivision Regulations, 1997 October (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Technical Master Plan, 1994 September (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Town Center Design Guidelines, 2001 January (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Wilton Wildfire Preserve and Park, [Promotional Brochure], Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Wilton, Zoning Ordinance, 1995 May (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Rensselaer County, 1937-2003; 3; 8.01 cubic ft.